esldiscussions.com 2019-01-27

# ESL Discussions: Lesson Plans for ESL / EFL - Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

**We respect your privacy.**

Please find below information about the security and privacy of your personal information and about the kind of data this website's web server automatically collects from visitors to ESL Discussions.com.

We do not ask you for personal information on this website, There is no need to log in and submit personal information to use ESL Discussions.com.

The web server ESL Discussions.com uses automatically collects anonymous information about visitors' activity to this website. It does this for security reasons to keep your visit safe. The data collected might be information such as your IP address, which web browser you used to visit, the date and time you visited this site, which pages you looked at on this site and for how long. It is impossible for us to know the name or other personal information of anyone who visits this website as we do not ask for any personal information. In addition, we do not sell any data or share it with third parties. 

**Data Security**

ESL Discussions.com is hosted on a server that uses 'https' technology. This encrypts all data sent to protect the security of your visit to this website and the safety of anything you download.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to obtain anonymous statistics and data about visits and traffic to ESL Discussions.com. This information helps us to see how people use our website, and this helps us make ESL Discussions.com better. If you do not want your visit to be logged by Google Analytics, please visit this page:

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

The web server ESL Discussions.com uses may use cookies to store information about your personal preferences when you visit our site. We do not sell or share information this information. If you prefer, you can turn off our cookies in your web browser settings, or your in anti-virus software.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use Google's AdSense program to serve ads on our website. The companies in the advertisements may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to serve you with more relevant advertisements that might be of greater interest to you. Some of these advertisers may use cookies or web beacons when they advertise on our site. They may gather information including your IP address, the web browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, if you have Flash installed. They will never know your name, home address, e-mail address, or telephone number. 

You can chose to disable or turn off third-party cookies in your browser settings. You can also choose to opt out of personalized advertising through Google's Privacy tools. More information about this is here:

_Google Privacy Tools_

By using our website, you agree to your data about your visit to our website being collected so we can provide a better website. If you do not agree to this, then you should not continue to use ESL Discussions.com.  

(Updated May 2018)
